Guide to the Peter E. Palmquist Collection of Male Photographers in the American West
Beinecke Rare Book and Manuscript Library
- Photographic Materials, circa 1840-2003; Series II; (231 boxes)
  - Photographic Materials
    - Bayley, Wilbur Fisk & Nathan J. (Box 346)
    - Bayley, Wilbur Fisk (Box 346)
    - Bayley's Photograph Gallery (Box 346)
    - Beach, Edward A. (Box 346)
    - Beal, Charles H., 3 (Box 346)
    - Beale & Craven (Box 346)
    - Beals & Walters (Box 348)
    - Beals & Waterhouse (Box 348)
    - Beals, Albert J. (Box 348)
    - Beals, Henry Sherman, 3 (Box 349)
    - Beals, T. L. (Box 348)
    - Bear Photo Service (Box 348)
    - Bearden, Andrew Jackson (Box 348)
    - Beatty, D. D. (Box 348)
    - Beaven & McSwigin (Box 348)
    - Beck Bros. (Box 348)
    - Beck, A. H. (Box 348)
    - Beck, Lou Westcott (Box 348)
    - Beck, T. (Box 348)
    - Beckwith, Charles D. (Box 348)
    - Beebe, A. P. (Box 348)
    - Behrendt, Richard (Box 348)
    - Bell & Company (Box 348)
    - Bell, William Abraham (Box 348)
    - Belle-Oudry, Edward H. (Box 348)
    - Bell's Studios (Box 348)
    - Bene, A. (Box 348)
    - Benecke, Robert (Box 348)
    - Benedickt, Carl (Box 348)
    - Benjamin (Box 348)
    - Bennett, Arthur J. G. (Box 348)
    - Bennett, C. N. (Box 348)
    - Bennett's Photo Service (Box 348)
    - Benning's Photo (Box 348)
    - Benson, Z. (Box 350)
    - Berg, J. (Box 350)
    - Bergeron (Box 350)
    - Berkeley Camera Club (Box 350)
    - Berminghan, H. de (Box 350)
    - Bertrand, Joseph T. (Box 350)
    - Best & Company (Box 350)
    - Best's Studio (Box 350)
    - Betancue & Ditmas (Box 350)
    - Betterly, G. S. (Box 350)
    - Biddell, George E. & Co. (Box 350)
    - Bierstadt, Albert (Box 350)
    - Bierstadt, Charles (Box 350)
    - Bijou Studio (Box 350)
    - Biles, C. W. (Box 350)
    - Billington, W. C. (Box 350)
    - Bingley, Photo-Engraving Company (Box 350)
    - Bird & Cook (Box 350)
    - Bird & Eilerman (Box 350)
    - Bird, John W. (Box 350)
    - Bisbee & Nye (Box 350)
    - Bisbee, J. A. (Box 350)
    - Blackhall, John (Box 351)
    - Blaine and Williams (Box 351)
    - Blair (Box 351)
    - Blaisdell, Samuel Stillman (Box 351)
    - Blake Studios (Box 351)
    - Blake, Alfred (Box 351)
    - Blakesly (Box 351)
    - Blakesly & Healy (Box 351)
    - Blakesly, H. H. (Box 351)
    - Blanchard, James B. (Box 351)
    - Blauert & Widder (Box 351)
    - Blome, John H. (Box 351)
    - Bluett & Fardon (Box 351)
    - Blumann, Sigismund (Box 351)
    - Bodwill, J. A. (Box 351)
    - Boehmer, Fred C. (Box 351)
    - Bolton & Strong (Box 351)
    - Bon Ton Gallery (Box 351)
    - Bonine, Elias A. (Box 351)
    - Borges (Box 351)
    - Bosco & Penelon (Box 351)
    - Boston Photograph Company (Box 351)
    - Boston Railroad Photo Car, 2 (Box 351)
    - Bosworth, A. H. (Box 351)
    - Bosworth, Francis Eugene (Box 351)
    - Bourne (Box 351)
    - Boussum, Charles, 3 (Box 352)
    - Bowen, C. Denton (Box 353)
    - Bowman & Leigh (Box 353)
    - Bowman, Walter S. (Box 353)
    - Bowman's (Box 353)
    - Boyd, Thomas Henry (Box 353)
    - Boyden, J. (Box 353)
    - Boydston, David S. (Box 353)
    - Boyé, Otto (Box 535)
    - Boyé & Habenicht (Box 353)
    - Boyes Springs Postal Studio (Box 353)
    - Boysen & Struckmann (Box 353)
    - Boysen, Iwer, 2 (Box 353)
    - Boyson, Julius Theodore (Box 353)
    - Bradley & Rulofson, 33 (Box 354)
    - Bradley & Rulofson (Box 355)
    - Bradley & Rulofson (Box 356)
    - Bradley, A. H. (Box 357)
    - Bradley, Henry William (Box 357)
    - Bradley, W. A. (Box 357)
    - Brady's (Box 357)
    - Brandon, J. H. (Box 357)
    - Brandt, Louis (Box 357)
    - Branin, R. C. (Box 357)
    - Brant, Eugene (Box 357)
    - Brayton, John Gray, 4 (Box 358)
    - Brewer (Box 357)
    - Brewster Photo Supplies (Box 357)
    - Brewster, J. C., 5 (Box 359)
    - Brickey, E. Marvin (Box 357)
    - Briggs (Box 357)
    - Briggs & Bailey (Box 357)
    - Briggs & Miller (Box 357)
    - Briggs, Egbert T. (Box 357)
    - Briggs, J. A. (Box 357)
    - Briggs, William (Box 357)
    - Brince, Herman (Box 357)
    - Brinkerhoff, A. Evelyn (Box 357)
    - Brinkmann, C. C. (Box 357)
    - Britt, Peter, 5 (Box 360)
    - Britt, Peter, 13 (Box 361)
    - Britton & Rey (Box 357)
    - Brock & Company (Box 357)
    - Brodeck & Company (Box 357)
    - Brodeck & Schroder (Box 357)
    - Brodeck, Henry Herman (Box 357)
    - Brooklyn Photo Studio (Box 357)
    - Brooks & Hyde (Box 357)
    - Brown (Box 357)
    - Brown & Edwards (Box 357)
    - Brown & Otto (Box 357)
    - Brown, John M. (Box 357)
    - Brown Kenneth (Box 357)
    - Brown, N. & Son (Box 357)
    - Brown, Nicholas (Box 357)
    - Brown, Thomas Arthur (Box 357)
    - Brown, W. (Box 357)
    - Brown, William Albert (Box 357)
    - Brown, William M. (Box 357)
    - Bruguiere, Francis J. (Box 362)
    - Bruguiere, P. S. (Box 362)
    - Brunt & Company (Box 362)
    - Bryan & Johnston (Box 362)
    - Bryan, John M. (Box 362)
    - Bryant, Charles C. (Box 362)
    - Buchtel & Stolte (Box 362)
    - Buchtel, Joseph (Box 362)
    - Buck, J. M. (Box 362)
    - Budden's Traveling Picture Gallery (Box 362)
    - Bud's Studio (Box 362)
    - Bunnell Photo Shop (Box 362)
    - Burge, J. C. (Box 362)
    - Burgess & Cann (Box 362)
    - Burgess, George Henry (Box 362)
    - Burgoyne, George (Box 362)
    - Burkett, Frederick (Box 362)
    - Burnett, 3 (Box 362)
    - Burnett & Ercanbrack (Box 362)
    - Burnett & Schach (Box 362)
    - Burnett & Slattery (Box 362)
    - Burnett, D. W. (Box 362)
    - Burton (Box 362)
    - Bush, Henry V., 4 (Box 363)
    - Bush, J. L. (Box 362)
    - Bushby & Company (Box 362)
    - Bushnell Photo Company, 15 (Box 364–365)
    - Bushnell, Fred H., 4 (Box 366)
    - Butler (Box 362)
    - Butler, B. D. (Box 362)
    - Butler, E. P. (Box 362)
    - Butler, George Rowell (Box 362)
    - Butterfield & Summers (Box 362)
    - Butterfield, Sampson H. (Box 362)
    - Button & Higgins (Box 362)
    - Caboni, E. (Box 367)
    - Cal Pictures (Box 367)
    - Calder, J. W. (Box 367)
    - California Camera Club (Box 367)
    - California Camera Company (Box 367)
    - California Card Manufacturing Company (Box 367)
    - California College of Photography (Box 367)
    - California Photo Company (Box 367)
    - California Photo-Engraving Company (Box 367)
    - California Photographic Gallery (Box 367)
    - California Railroad Photo Car (Box 367)
    - California Studio (Box 367)
    - Camera Club (Box 367)
    - Camera Corner (Box 367)
    - Camera Craft (Box 367)
    - Camera Shop (Box 367)
    - Camp Beale Photo Studios (Box 367)
    - Campbell, L. D. (Box 367)
    - Camps (Box 367)
    - Candid Camera Photo Service Company (Box 367)
    - Cann, William Jr. (Box 367)
    - Cannon, Marsena (Box 367)
    - Cantwell, H. C. (Box 367)
    - Capps, A. V. (Box 367)
    - Capwell (Box 367)
    - Carbanati, H. (Box 367)
    - Carbutt, John (Box 367)
    - Carden, Robert A. (Box 367)
    - Cardinell-Vincent Company (Box 367)
    - Cardwell, J. R. (Box 367)
    - Carhenter (Box 367)
    - Carlson, Charles H. (Box 367)
    - Carmen, The (Box 367)
    - Carpenter (Box 367)
    - Carpenter, A. O., 9 (Box 368)
    - Carr, Richard (Box 367)
    - Carruthers, 2 (Box 367)
    - Carter, Charles W. (Box 367)
    - Casper's Studio (Box 367)
    - Cass (Box 367)
    - Castro, Rafael (Box 367)
    - Catalina View Depot (Box 367)
    - Catterlin, F. J. (Box 367)
    - Central Art Company (Box 367)
    - Chalmers, James Calder, Jr. (Box 367)
    - Chamberlain, William Gunnison (Box 367)
    - Chandler, J. W. & Company (Box 367)
    - Chapman, James S. (Box 367)
    - Charlemagne, The (Box 367)
    - Charlton, E. F. & Company (Box 369)
    - Chase, Edwin S. (Box 369)
    - Chavez, M. D. (Box 369)
    - Chenhall, John (Box 369)
    - Cherry, Edgar (Box 369)
    - Chicago Gallery (Box 369)
    - Chico Book Store (Box 369)
    - Children's Studio (Box 369)
    - China Pharmacy (Box 369)
    - Christian & Coover (Box 369)
    - Churchman, S. E. (Box 369)
    - Chutes (Box 369)
    - Cilley, Earl M. (Box 369)
    - City Mart Photo Studio (Box 369)
    - Clapp, J.C. (Box 369)
    - Clark (Box 369)
    - Clark (Box 369)
    - Clark & Loftus (Box 369)
    - Clark, E. L., 3 (Box 369)
    - Clark, Edward A. (Box 369)
    - Clark, G. P. (Box 369)
    - Clark, G. W. (Box 369)
    - Clausen, Christian H. (Box 369)
    - Clavering, Robert K. (Box 369)
    - Clayton, James A., 4 (Box 369)
    - Clemensen, Charles (Box 369)
    - Clements (Box 369)
    - Clements & Sprague (Box 369)
    - Clements & Tong (Box 369)
    - Clements, E. F. (Box 369)
    - Clendenon, Lewis K. (Box 369)
    - Cliff Photo Gallery (Box 370)
    - Clifford, Granville (Box 370)
    - Clinch & Tucker (Box 370)
    - Clinch, W. A., 3 (Box 371)
    - Clute, Fayette J., 2 (Box 370)
    - Clyburn, Les (Box 370)
    - Cobb, David (Box 370)
    - Cobb, W. (Box 370)
    - Coffin, Isaac T. (Box 370)
    - Cohen, Edgar A., 2 (Box 370)
    - Cohen, Herrman (Box 370)
    - Cohen, M. L. & Company (Box 370)
    - Cohen's Camera Center (Box 370)
    - Coillot's Camera Shop (Box 370)
    - Colby, Howard (Box 370)
    - Cole & Downing (Box 370)
    - Coleman (Box 370)
    - Coleman, Kee (Box 370)
    - Collier, Charles T. (Box 370)
    - Collinge, & Foster (Box 370)
    - Collins & Clements (Box 370)
    - Collins, P. T. (Box 370)
    - Collom, George C. (Box 370)
    - Collom, W. N. (Box 370)
    - Colton, C. (Box 370)
    - Columbian Art Gallery (Box 370)
    - Comings, E. S. (Box 370)
    - Commercial Art Company (Box 370)
    - Conaway, B. F. (Box 370)
    - Cone, F. E. (Box 370)
    - Conklin & Company (Box 370)
    - Connell, Will (Box 370)
    - Continent Stereoscopic Company (Box 370)
    - Cook & Butler (Box 372)
    - Cook & Newton (Box 372)
    - Cook & Schneider (Box 372)
    - Cook, F. A. (Box 372)
    - Cook, J. E. (Box 372)
    - Cook, W. B., 2 (Box 372)
    - Cook, William H. (Box 372)
    - Cook's Art Studio (Box 372)
    - Coombs, Frederick C., 6 (Box 373)
    - Coonley, J. F. (Box 372)
    - Coover (Box 372)
    - Coover & Rasmussen (Box 372)
    - Coover Studio (Box 372)
    - Corinne Gift Shop (Box 372)
    - Cosmopolitan Art and Photographic Company (Box 372)
    - Cottage Gallery (Box 372)
    - Cottrell, D. E. (Box 372)
    - Coules & Westervelt (Box 372)
    - Coules, Charles J. (Box 372)
    - Cowles, L. (Box 372)
    - Cox & Fuller (Box 372)
    - Coyle (Box 372)
    - Craig & Mosher (Box 374)
    - Craig-Lee Photo (Box 374)
    - Cramer, Charles Lake, 12 (Box 375)
    - Crandall, B. W. (Box 374)
    - Crandall, Charles F. (Box 374)
    - Crane, P. L. (Box 374)
    - Crawford, 2 (Box 374)
    - Crawford, E. L. (Box 374)
    - Crawford, J. G. (Box 374)
    - Crescent Art Gallery (Box 374)
    - Crescent Photo Company (Box 374)
    - Crescent Studio (Box 374)
    - Crissman, J. (Box 374)
    - Crocker, H. S. (Box 374)
    - Crockwell, J. H. (Box 374)
    - Cromwell & Westervelt (Box 374)
    - Cross & Dimmitt (Box 374)
    - Crow, Samuel B. (Box 374)
    - Crow, Samuel M. (Box 374)
    - Crown Studio (Box 374)
    - Crutchfield, Benjamin F. (Box 374)
    - Cunningham, A. N. (Box 374)
    - Cunningham, E. N. (Box 374)
    - Cunningham, R. (Box 374)
    - Cunningham's Art Studio Car (Box 374)
    - Currie, Lorenzo D. (Box 374)
    - Currier & Winter (Box 374)
    - Curtis, Edward Sheriff, 2 (Box 374)
    - Curtiss, E. H. (Box 374)
    - Cushing, Edward (Box 374)
    - Cutberth, Will G., 3 (Box 374)
    - Daggett, J. R., 19 (Box 376)
    - Daguerre (Box 377)
    - Dall, John H. (Box 377)
    - Dames & Arrowsmith (Box 378)
    - Dames & Butler (Box 378)
    - Dames & Company, 5 (Box 378)
    - Dames & Dorsaz (Box 378)
    - Dames & Hayes, 3 (Box 378)
    - Dames & Keil (Box 378)
    - Dames & Williams (Box 378)
    - Damron (Box 377)
    - Dana & Peterson (Box 377)
    - Dando, Farnham C. (Box 377)
    - Daniel & Byrd (Box 377)
    - Danielson, C. L. (Box 377)
    - Darkroom, The (Box 377)
    - Darlington, Charles A. (Box 377)
    - Darragh, J. C. (Box 377)
    - Dassonville, W. E. (Box 377)
    - Datesman, Peter (Box 377)
    - Davey, Frank, 2 (Box 377)
    - Davidson (Box 377)
    - Davidson Brothers (Box 377)
    - Davidson, E. M., 2 (Box 377)
    - Davidson, I. G. (Box 377)
    - Davidson, N. R. (Box 377)
    - Davies Studio (Box 377)
    - Davis & Zwisler (Box 377)
    - Davis, Walter (Box 377)
    - Davis, Wayne (Box 377)
    - De Buhr, Joseph (Box 379)
    - De Cosmos, Amor (Box 379)
    - De Silver (Box 379)
    - Dealey (Box 379)
    - Dean & Gay (Box 379)
    - Dean, Frank E. (Box 379)
    - Dean, O. S. (Box 379)
    - Decker, George (Box 379)
    - Decker, H. W. (Box 379)
    - Dee (Box 379)
    - Dee, Joe (Box 379)
    - Defender Photo Supply Company (Box 379)
    - DeGroat & Kellogg (Box 379)
    - DeLong, Charles E. (Box 379)
    - DeLuxe (Box 379)
    - DeMorat, O. B. (Box 379)
    - Denevi (Box 379)
    - Denison & Howard (Box 379)
    - Denison News Company (Box 379)
    - Denison, F. H., 2 (Box 379)
    - Denke, Augustus Jr. (Box 379)
    - Denninger, Arthur G. (Box 379)
    - Denny, Oliver (Box 379)
    - Denver Galleries (Box 379)
    - Derby, Charles (Box 379)
    - Desmond & Sutterley (Box 379)
    - Desmond, Robert Auxley (Box 379)
    - D'Estrella, Theophilus (Box 379)
    - Detroit Photographic Company (Box 379)
    - Dewey (Box 379)
    - Dexter Press Inc. (Box 380)
    - D'Heureuse, Rudolph (Box 374)
    - Dickenson, John C. (Box 380)
    - Dickman, W. (Box 380)
    - Dickson, Henry A. (Box 380)
    - Dijeau & Severin (Box 380)
    - Dijeau, Alex (Box 380)
    - Dillon Laboratories (Box 380)
    - Dimick, F. E. (Box 380)
    - Ditmas, H. (Box 380)
    - Dix (Box 380)
    - Do Mar Company (Box 380)
    - Dolores Studio (Box 380)
    - Donnell (Box 380)
    - Dopp, John C. (Box 380)
    - Doran, J. T. (Box 380)
    - Doré Studio, 8 (Box 381)
    - Dorman Bros. (Box 380)
    - Dornin, George, 3 (Box 380)
    - Dorr, James, 2 (Box 380)
    - Dorsaz, Frederick H., 2 (Box 380)
    - Dougall, Wm. (Box 380)
    - Dove & Moeller (Box 380)
    - Dowd, F. B. (Box 380)
    - Dowe (Box 380)
    - Dowe & Murphy (Box 382)
    - Dowe & Painter (Box 382)
    - Dowe, A. W. (Box 382)
    - Dowe, D. W., 2 (Box 382)
    - Dowe, Lewis (Box 382)
    - Dowe, O. L. (Box 382)
    - Downey, B. A., 2 (Box 382)
    - Downey, W. M. & Son (Box 382)
    - Downing Bros., 2 (Box 382)
    - Downing, Joseph H., 2 (Box 382)
    - Downing, Rea & Rauscher (Box 382)
    - Dresser, 2 (Box 382)
    - Duhem & Lathrop (Box 382)
    - Duhem Bros. (Box 382)
    - Duhem, Albert (Box 382)
    - Dunham, Allen Murry, 3 (Box 382)
    - Dunham, O. W. (Box 382)
    - Duperly, Henri Louis (Box 382)
    - Durgan, Frank (Box 382)
    - Dutton, S. (Box 382)
    - Dyba, Edward (Box 382)
    - Dyeau & Severen (Box 382)
    - Dyer & Luders (Box 382)
    - Dyer, W. D. (Box 382)
    - Eardley & Van Diveer (Box 383)
    - Easterly & Company (Box 383)
    - Eastman (Box 383)
    - Eastman Kodak Stores (Box 383)
    - Eastman View Company (Box 383)
    - Eastman, G. L. (Box 383)
    - Eastman, G. S. (Box 383)
    - Eastman, J. H., 2 (Box 383)
    - Eastman's Studio (Box 383)
    - Easton, James Hiram (Box 383)
    - Eddy (Box 383)
    - Edelen, Jim (Box 383)
    - Edgerton, H. H. (Box 383)
    - Edouart, Alexander, 13 (Box 384)
    - Edson, Norman (Box 383)
    - Edwards, J. E., 2 (Box 383)
    - Edwards, John Paul (Box 383)
    - Egbert, William P. (Box 383)
    - Ehmann, Charles E. (Box 383)
    - Eichenberger Bros. (Box 383)
    - Eichenberger, Emil (Box 383)
    - Eichler, L. O. (Box 383)
    - Eilerman (Box 385)
    - Elderman, Ferdinand (Box 385)
    - Eldridge, Irving (Box 385)
    - Eldridge, J. E. (Box 385)
    - Elite, 18 (Box 386)
    - Elliott, Orman, 9 (Box 387)
    - Ellis & Goodwin (Box 388)
    - Emanuel, E. V. (Box 385)
    - Emerson, James H. (Box 385)
    - Emetaz, Roland (Box 385)
    - Empire Studios (Box 385)
    - Emporium & Golden Rule Bazaar, The (Box 385)
    - Engle (Box 385)
    - Eppler, A. O. (Box 385)
    - Erickson, Henry (Box 385)
    - Erwin, J. W. (Box 385)
    - Esmay, John (Box 385)
    - Esterle, A. M. (Box 385)
    - Ette, Oscar (Box 385)
    - Etter, Burton, 2 (Box 385)
    - Eureka Gallery (Daguerrean Rooms) (Box 385)
    - Evans & Van Etten (Box 385)
    - Evans, F. E., 2 (Box 385)
    - Everitt, Elias F. (Box 385)
    - Excelsior Studio (Box 385)
    - F/Stop Pizza Parlor (Box 388)
    - Faber Foto Art Studio (Box 388)
    - Fad, The (Box 388)
    - Fagersteen, Gustavus (Box 388)
    - Fairbanks & DeBuhr (Box 388)
    - Fairbanks, W. H. (Box 388)
    - Fairbanks, W. W., 6 (Box 389)
    - Faist, Charles G. (Box 388)
    - Falkenshield, Andrew (Box 388)
    - Family Camera Store, The (Box 388)
    - Faol, Henry (Box 388)
    - Fardon, George Robinson, 2 (Box 388)
    - Farguliar, Francis (Box 388)
    - Farrar & Horstmann (Box 388)
    - Fassold, Peter (Box 388)
    - Fawcett. E. E. (Box 388)
    - Fayette (Box 388)
    - Federal Photo Studios (Box 388)
    - Fell (Box 388)
    - Fell & Van Burkleo (Box 388)
    - Fell, A. W., 3 (Box 388)
    - Fellows, Homer (Box 388)
    - Felt, J. W. (Box 388)
    - Fenn, S. T. (Box 388)
    - Ferndale Gallery (Box 388)
    - Ferrand, Charles (Box 388)
    - Ferry Studio, The (Box 388)
    - Field (Box 388)
    - Finch Photo Studio (Box 388)
    - Fine Art Portrait Academy (Box 388)
    - Fink, J. F., 2 (Box 388)
    - Fischer, Adolp (Box 388)
    - Fischer, M. (Box 388)
    - Fishbourne & Gow (Box 390)
    - Fiske, George (Box 390)
    - Fitch, Walter T., 10 (Box 391)
    - Fitzhugh, Lee (Box 390)
    - Flaglor & DuRose (Box 392)
    - Flaglor & Parker (Box 392)
    - Flaglor, A. P., 5 (Box 392)
    - Flanders & Godfrey (Box 390)
    - Fleckenstein, Louis (Box 390)
    - Florence Photographic Gallery (Box 390)
    - Flower & Bryant (Box 390)
    - Flower & Bryant (Box 390)
    - Fly, C. S. (Box 390)
    - Fong, Edward (Box 390)
    - Foley, D. J. (Box 390)
    - Fong, Edward (Box 390)
    - Fong, Gary (Box 390)
    - Forbes, Robert L. (Box 390)
    - Ford, James M., 3 (Box 390)
    - Forell, C. (Box 390)
    - Fortune, E. W. (Box 390)
    - Foss & Halsey (Box 390)
    - Foss, Oscar, 3 (Box 390)
    - Foster, A. W. (Box 390)
    - Foster, L. J. (Box 390)
    - Fowler Studio (Box 393)
    - Fowzer & Samuels (Box 394)
    - Fowzer, George J. (Box 394)
    - Fowzer, Jacob, 6 (Box 394)
    - Fox & Symons (Box 390)
    - Fox, Andrew J. (Box 390)
    - Francis, F. J. (Box 390)
    - Franklin & Howell (Box 390)
    - Franklin, B. J. (Box 390)
    - Franklin, J. C., 2 (Box 390)
    - Franklin, Maurice A. (Box 390)
    - Fraser, George (Box 390)
    - Frasher, Burton, Sr., 3 (Box 395)
    - Fredrick, Harry (Box 395)
    - Freeman, E. R. (Box 395)
    - Freeman, Lee (Box 395)
    - French, I. G. (Box 395)
    - Friedlander, Otto (Box 395)
    - Friend, Arnold Oscar (Box 395)
    - Friend, Herve (Box 395)
    - Frost, Eugene (Box 395)
    - Frye & Jenkins (Box 395)
    - Frye, H. H., 4 (Box 395)
    - Fryett, F. C. (Box 395)
    - Fuller, William H., 2 (Box 395)
    - Fullerton (Box 395)
    - Fulton, G. O. (Box 395)
    - Furlong, James N. (Box 395)
    - Furman, Robert (Box 395)
    - Fusaki Photo Studio (Box 395)
    - Gage, H. K. (Box 396)
    - Gagne, Edward (Box 396)
    - Gaines, F. H. (Box 396)
    - Garden City Photo Company (Box 396)
    - Gardiner, R. H., 2 (Box 396)
    - Gardner, George (Box 396)
    - Gardner, W. S. (Box 396)
    - Garthorne, Charles Andrew (Box 396)
    - Gasberg, J. C. (Box 396)
    - Gaston, Paul de (Box 396)
    - Gates Studio (Box 396)
    - Gates, Franklin Q. (Box 396)
    - Gearing, J. E. (Box 396)
    - Gehres, F. J. (Box 396)
    - Geldert (Box 396)
    - Gem Studio (Box 396)
    - Genthe, Arnold, 2 (Box 396)
    - Gentile, Charles (Box 396)
    - Genuit, J. H. (Box 396)
    - Gesler, Fred (Box 396)
    - Ghost Town Pitchur Gallery (Box 396)
    - Giannini (Box 396)
    - Gilbert, E. C. (Box 396)
    - Gilbert, George H., 5 (Box 397)
    - Gilfillan, A. W. (Box 398)
    - Gilhousen Bros., 2 (Box 398)
    - Gillett's Photographic Studio (Box 398)
    - Gilroy Photo Gallery (Box 398)
    - Girschick, Hans (Box 398)
    - Givens, J. D. (Box 398)
    - Givens, L. P. (Box 398)
    - Glasou, T. J. (Box 398)
    - Gleason, Herbert (Box 398)
    - Globe Portrait Company (Box 398)
    - Godeus, John D., 6 (Box 399)
    - Godfrey, William M., 2 (Box 398)
    - Goebel, R. (Box 398)
    - Goetz, Henry J. R. (Box 400)
    - Golden West Art Gallery (Box 400)
    - Goldsmith Bros. (Box 400)
    - Golsh, Arthur C. (Box 400)
    - Gonzales, Pedro (Box 400)
    - Goodpasture (Box 400)
    - Goodrich & Phear (Box 400)
    - Gosting, George G. (Box 400)
    - Goudy Bros. (Box 400)
    - Gove, O. M., 2 (Box 400)
    - Gowland, Peter (Box 400)
    - Graham Photo Company, 2 (Box 400)
    - Graham, L. A. (Box 400)
    - Gran Studio (Box 400)
    - Grand Art Gallery (Box 400)
    - Grand Central Studio (Box 400)
    - Grand Post Card Studio (Box 400)
    - Graves, H. D. (Box 400)
    - Graves, S. F. (Box 400)
    - Graves, T. L. (Box 400)
    - Graybiel, E. (Box 400)
    - Grazzini, F. (Box 400)
    - Green Studio, 2 (Box 400)
    - Green, A. H. (Box 400)
    - Gregory, 3 (Box 400)
    - Griffith Photo Service (Box 400)
    - Griffiths, P. W., 7 (Box 401)
    - Groff, A. J. (Box 400)
    - Gross, Anton (Box 400)
    - Grove (Box 400)
    - Grove & Stinson (Box 400)
    - Grove, E. K. (Box 400)
    - Grove, L. (Box 400)
    - Guarantee Photo Company (Box 400)
    - Guerin, F. W. (Box 400)
    - Gulick, Chas. (Box 400)
    - Gurnsey, Byron H. (Box 400)
    - H. C. M. (Box 402)
    - Haas & Schreiner (Box 402)
    - Habenicht, George, 3 (Box 402)
    - Haggard, Walter J. (Box 402)
    - Hagman, Ossian (Box 402)
    - Hall, J. T. (Box 402)
    - Hall, Robert (Box 402)
    - Hallman, A. (Box 402)
    - Halsey & Coffin (Box 402)
    - Halsey & Scripture (Box 402)
    - Halsey, Andrew J. (Box 402)
    - Halsey, H. H. (Box 402)
    - Halsey, I. S. (Box 402)
    - Halverson, E. K. (Box 402)
    - Hamaker, Harry (Box 402)
    - Hamaker, Harry L. (Box 402)
    - Hamilton & Kellogg (Box 402)
    - Hamilton & Lovering (Box 402)
    - Hamilton & Shew (Box 402)
    - Hamilton & Starr (Box 402)
    - Hamilton & Tidball (Box 402)
    - Hamilton, C. F., 2 (Box 402)
    - Hamilton, E. C. (Box 402)
    - Hamilton, Tidball, & Morse (Box 402)
    - Hammersmith, John E. (Box 402)
    - Hammond, Bill (Box 402)
    - Hance & Mast (Box 402)
    - Handley, J. C. (Box 402)
    - Hanscom, Moses, Jr. (Box 402)
    - Hansen, Jacob, 5 (Box 403)
    - Hanson, F. H. (Box 402)
    - Hanson, John A. (Box 402)
    - Harada Studio (Box 402)
    - Harder's (Box 402)
    - Hardesty, Frank B. (Box 404)
    - Hardy, Frank R. (Box 404)
    - Hardy, J., 3 (Box 404)
    - Harker, J. W. (Box 404)
    - Harkness & Mitchell (Box 404)
    - Harkness, F. M., 2 (Box 404)
    - Harrington (Box 404)
    - Harrington, William H., 4 (Box 405)
    - Harris, Al (Box 404)
    - Harris, W., 7 (Box 406)
    - Harris, Walt (Box 404)
    - Harrod (Box 404)
    - Harting Portrait House (Box 404)
    - Hartsook, Fred J., 9 (Box 408)
    - Harvey, George H. (Box 404)
    - Harvey's New York Photographic Gallery (Box 404)
    - Haskell, Walter S. (Box 404)
    - Haussler, F. O., 8 (Box 409)
    - Hawes & Schroder (Box 407)
    - Hawes, Alvin Lawrence (Box 404)
    - Hawks, N. C. (Box 404)
    - Hay, Robt. F. (Box 404)
    - Hayes & Fowzer (Box 404)
    - Haynes (Box 404)
    - Hayward & Muzzall (Box 404)
    - Haywood & Deyer (Box 404)
    - Hazeltine, M. M., 7 (Box 402)
    - Hazlett, J. W. (Box 404)
    - Head, T. D. (Box 411)
    - Healy, E. R. (Box 411)
    - Heath (Box 411)
    - Heath, Charles E. (Box 411)
    - Hecht, T. H. (Box 411)
    - Hedger, Henry A. (Box 411)
    - Hedum & Bishop (Box 411)